mindray.com 2017-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Mindray North America

Mindray DS USA, Inc. (“Mindray”) is strongly committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. Please carefully read the following Privacy Policy.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain the type of information that Mindray collects from our users on this site and in the course of the relationship, what we do with that information, and how users can update and control the use of information provided on this site. Please note that this policy may change from time to time so please check it frequently. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Any changes to this policy will be considered effective immediately upon posting. This Policy was last revised on 12/6/2013 and became effective that day.

**I. User Consent to Policy**

Any person accessing, browsing, or otherwise using the site shall be considered a “User.” All Users are bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. Users consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of User information pursuant to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**II. Type of Information We Collect:**

A. Contact Information

You are welcome to browse some portions of the web site without becoming a registered user. For some services or areas on the site, specifically to order product, we will ask that you register if you have not already done so and provide us with information about you and/or your company such as name, job title, email address, and other types of information which enable us to provide services and information to you. Once we provide you with a user name and password you will be able to order product.

B. Credit and Financial Information

Currently, our online orders are treated identically to other orders, including those made over the phone. All new customers need to be approved by Mindray’s credit department, which may request further information, including but not limited to financial information, equipment information, and other personal information; this information will not be collected through the web site. We may collect other personal information when you provide comments or participate in surveys.

C. Human Resources Information

Our Human Resources staff may review and process your job application and/or resume submitted through [jobs@mindray.com](mailto:jobs@mindray.com) or other employment websites or services. If no opportunities are available at this time, we may keep your information on file for purposes of identifying future employment opportunities for you at Mindray.

Please note that employment websites or services are third-party websites/services that are not affiliated with Mindray and are not governed by Mindray’s Privacy Policy or Terms of Use. Please contact these websites/services for information regarding their privacy policies.

D. Browsing and Technical Information

Mindray may also collect aggregate information about the use of our site, such as which pages are most frequently visited, how many users we receive daily, and how long users stay on each page.

**III. Cookies**

The site may make use of two types of cookies. “Cookies” are small data files, typically made up of a string of text and numbers, which assign you a unique identifier. A “client cookie” may be sent to your browser so that our systems remember your requests and keep track of the pages you view on our site and which services you use. A “server cookie” may be maintained on our systems to recognize you when you return to the site. This information allows us to better administer the site and provide a more tailored and user friendly service to you. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being sent; if so, you may limit the functionality Mindray can provide you when you visit the site.

**IV. Security**

Mindray strives to have in place appropriate means to protect your information. However, in providing your information over a public or third party network, you do so at your own risk. Mindray makes no representation or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of its security measures.

**V. Use Of The Information We Collect:**

The information about you, which you provide and we collect in the course of our relationship, is used to facilitate your orders or other activities between us, and to provide you with both general and tailored information about offers, products, services or other useful information from us or others. If you order products or services from us, we may maintain an order history for your account. We also may combine information you have provided to us in communications offline with the information you have given us online (or vice versa), to provide a more customized experience for you when you deal with us. We may use demographic and site usage information collected from users to improve the usefulness of our site and to prepare aggregate, non-identifying, information used in marketing, site advertising, or similar activities.

By visiting our web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of our company we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy, for the purposes identified in our other communications with you, or to provide the information to other Mindray businesses or subsidiaries which may be outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located in other jurisdictions. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.

Personal data relating to an identified or identifiable individual that is submitted to this site will be collected, processed, stored, and disposed of in accordance with applicable U.S. law. U.S. law, however, may not provide the degree of protection to personal data which is available in other countries. The submission of personal data constitutes the User’s acknowledgement that s/he has read and understood this notice, and agrees to its terms. As our services evolve, the types of information we collect may change. Please check this policy frequently for the most current explanation of our data practices.

**VI. With Whom Do We Share Information?**

We do not sell, rent or lease your email address or other personally identifying information to third parties. We may, however, share your information with companies affiliated with Mindray to achieve the purposes identified in this policy, in our other communications with you, or on the site.

We may provide to others the aggregate statistics about our customers’ orders or related site activity for purposes of marketing or promotion.

We may disclose information about you to others if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Mindray or others.

**VII. Third Party Websites**

Other companies that provide services on our site, that provide a co-branded version of our site, or that advertise or link on our site, may use cookies or collect other information about you when you go to their site. Mindray does not control the collection or use of information by these companies. You should contact these companies directly if you have any questions about their collection or use of information about you. Mindray’s privacy policy does not govern the privacy practices of these other companies or websites. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

**VIII. Opting Out, Accessing Or Changing Information**

Mindray maintains customer information, including order history and site usage data, for a length of time appropriate to our business needs. You may contact us at [privacyofficer@mindray.com](mailto:privacyofficer@mindray.com) or at (201) 995-8000 to correct or update any personal identifying information which you have submitted to us, or should you have questions about information maintained by us. If you operate in the European Union or other jurisdictions that provide access rights under law, you may access your personal information or have it corrected or updated in accordance with applicable law by contacting us. In some jurisdictions, you may be charged a reasonable fee for access to information.

**IX. Sale of Customer Data**

At this time, Mindray does not sell its customer data, however, as we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy business assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event that Mindray or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

**X. Site not for Children**

This site is not directed at children 13 years of age or under and Mindray does not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or under through the site.

**Questions or Concerns?**

Please feel free to contact us at [privacyofficer@mindray.com](mailto:privacyofficer@mindray.com) or at (201) 995-8000 if you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy or about Mindray’s collection of your information.
